Guide to the Mix Collection 1970-2001 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS 143
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES VIII: 1994
  - Subseries G: Media
    - Title: Ooh, Life is Juicy, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1417)
      Director: Goldwater, Helena
    - Title: Lawnbutch, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1418)
      Old number: 200
      Director: Farrell, Nicci
    - Title: Land Beyond Tomorrow, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1419)
      Old number: 201
      Director: Cederbaum, S.R. and Farell[sic], Nicci
    - Title: Her Appetite, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1420)
      Old number: 202
      Director: Fullman, Katrina
    - Title: Cinema Al-Fouad, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1421)
      Old number: 207
      Director: Soueid, Mohamed
    - Title: The Mister Sisters, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1422)
      Old number: 210
      Director: Wilhite, Ingrid
    - Title: Dark Sun, Bright Shade, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1423)
      Old number: 214
      Director: KWOI
    - Title: [1.]--Another American Family - Trailer [2.]--Boys/Life, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1424)
      Old number: 215
      Director: Roth, Phillip B.
    - Title: Vacancy, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1425)
      Old number: 217
      Director: Katsapetses, Nick
    - Title: [1.]--Blu Fiction [2.]--La Luce Sul Sentiero, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1426)
      Old number: 218
    - Title: [1.]--Era Meglio Morire Da Piccoli [2.]--L'amore Vincitore [3.]--Amore Perfetto, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1427)
      Old number: 220
    - Title: Olufina Abuela Balanquet, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1428)
      Old number: 221
    - Title: Smoke, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1429)
      Old number: 222
    - Title: Open For Flavor, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1430)
      Old number: 225
      Director: Torr, Diane
    - Title: Sepia's Blues, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1431)
      Old number: 230
      Director: Bridgforth, Sharon
    - Title: Scrub Me Mama, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1432)
      Old number: 231
      Director: Grotell, David
    - Title: Texas, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1433)
      Old number: 235
      Director: Gonzalez, Mari Keiko
    - Title: Kitchen Table Sex: Things I Like to Eat, Screened: [1994] (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1434)
      Old number: 236
      Director: L[e]der, Evie
    - Title: Salamander, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1435)
      Old number: 238
      Director: Syed, Tanya
    - Title: [1.]--Alimentiveness [2.]--Scrub, [1.]--Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1436)
      Old number: 240
      Director: Acosta, Roger
    - Title: Jane, Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1437)
      Old number: 242
      Director: Taylor, Mark
    - Title: [1.]--Go Down Slow [2.]--Lapse, [1.]--Screened: 1994 (Box 17, Folder ID: 143.1438)
      Old number: 243
      Director: [1.]--Warm, Luke [2.]--Daniel, James
    - Title: On The Track, Screened: 1995 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1439)
      Director: Holland, Sandra R.
    - Title: Good Machine (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1440)
      Director: Cohn, Roy and Smith, Jack
    - Title: [1.]--Diva [2.]--Limpasse [3.]--Angel [4.]--Whatever Happened to Dana Plato [5.]--The Voices of the [Fallers?] (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1441)
      Director: Johnston, Dennis
    - Title: Brincando El Charco, Screened: 1994 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1442)
      Director: Negron-Muntaner, Frances
    - Title: Lily White (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1443)
      Old number: #3 80486
      Director: Laba, Jaba
    - Title: [1.]--Bridgette [2.]--French Bitch, [2.]--Screened: 1994 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1444)
      Director: Tourette, Pussy
    - Title: Get It, Girl: Lesbians Talk About Sex, Screened: [1994] (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1445)
      Director: Turner, Kay and Gant, Ella
    - Title: Lily and Lu-Lu Go To The March, Screened: 1994 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1446)
      Director: Marnell, Lily and Moreira, Luciana
    - Title: Wax Me, Screened: 1994 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1447)
      Director: Simpson, Kelli
    - Title: ¡Viva 16!, Screened: [1994] (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1448)
    - Title: Worms, Beer, Matzoh, Screened: [1994] (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1449)
      Director: Callahan, Jennifer
    - Title: Deviant Beauty (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1450)
      Director: Keane, Tina
    - Title: Taking Back the Dolls, Screened: [1994] (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1451)
      Director: Singer, Leslie
    - Title: Outlaw, Screened: [1994] (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1452)
      Director: Lebow, Alisa
    - Title: When Shirley Met Florence, Screened: 1994 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1453)
      Director: Bezalel, Ronit
    - Title: [1.]--Bridgette [2.]--French Bitch, [2.]--Screened: 1994 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1454)
    - Title: No Fairy Tale, Screened: 1994 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1455)
      Director: Morgana, Aimee
    - Title: [1.]--The Butts [2.]--Safe Sex (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1456)
    - Title: Act Up/Diva TV Public Access Compilation (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1457)
      Director: Kramer, Larry
    - Title: Particularly Now, In Spring., Screened: 1995 (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1458)
      Old number: 29702
      Director: Defurne, Bavo
    - Title: [untitled], [no label] (Box 18, Folder ID: 143.1459)
    - Title: [1.]--Ataxiaflagris [2.]--Birth [3.]--Xycoprosis [4.]--Give, [1.]--Screened: 1994 (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1182)
      Old number: 229
      Director: Carter, Chad
    - Title: Heaven Earth and Hell, Screened: 1994, 1996 (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1186)
      Old number: 4, 131
    - Title: A Woman's Heart (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1220)
      Director: Mariae, Omri
    - Title: Is There A Cure For My Friend?, Screened: 1994 (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1223)
      Director: Lauber, Liza and Maidoff, Natasha
    - Title: [1.]--Momentary Lapses [2.]--Romeo's Flavor, [2.]--Screened: 1994 (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1225)
      Director: Turner, Kieran A.
    - Title: Frankie and Jocie, Screened: 1994, 1996 (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1243)
      Old number: V05
      Director: Taylor, Jocelyn
    - Title: Barbie Liberation Organizaion (BLO) Nightly News, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1569)
    - Title: The Easy Garden, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1651)
      Director: Stanley, Anie
    - Title: [1.]-- What Is a Line? [2.]-- A Cosmic Demonstration of Sexuality, Screened: [1995, 1998] (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1652)
    - Title: She Makes Love With Her, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1659)
      Director: Shmuel, Nili
    - Title: No Fairy Tale, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1671)
      Director: Morgana, Amy
    - Title: Virus, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1672)
      Director: Gaffney, Stuart
      Duration: [5] minutes
    - Title: [1.]-- Gasp [2.]-- Ajax for Life [3.]-- Light Sweet Crude, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1674)
      Director: Nerwen, Diane
    - Title: Cold Bath, Screened: 1994 (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1675)
      Director: Orr, Steve
    - Title: Rootless Cosmopolitans, Screened: 1992 (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1676)
      Director: Novaczek, Ruth
    - Title: [1.]-- Problems Around the Bike [2.]-- The Two Again, Screened: [1994] (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1687)
      Old number: 16M
      Director: [1.]-- Venclova, Andrey [2.]-- Mamushev, Vladislav
      Duration: [20] minutes
    - Title: A Short Film About Us, Screened: [1996] (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1689)
      Director: [Smith, Rita]
    - Title: Seducing Maarya, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1705)
      Old number: 421 0
      Director: [Hoe, Hunt]
      Duration: 112 minutes
    - Title: Isaak, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1706)
      Old number: 241
    - Title: Chasing the Moon, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1710)
      Old number: 170
      Duration: [40] minutes
    - Title: Cling Film, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1711)
      Old number: 33
      Director: Thew, Anna
    - Title: The Love Machine, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1713)
      Old number: 94
      Director: Snee, Patrick
    - Title: Unforgiven Fire, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1714)
      Old number: 34
      Director: Killacky, John and S. Grandell
    - Title: From a Secret Place, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1716)
      Old number: 26
      Director: Heller, Karin and Bill Domonkos
    - Title: A Light on the Path, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1717)
      Director: Puccioni, Marco
    - Title: Shades, Screened: Unknown (Box 19, Folder ID: 143.1722)
    - Title: Bloody Well Done, Screened: 1994 (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1245)
      Director: Percillier, Natalie
    - Title: A Woman's Heart, Screened: 1994 (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1474)
      Old number: 67166 #1
      Director: Marian, Omri
    - Title: Bloody Well Done, Screened: [1994] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1531)
    - Title: It's a Mitzvah, Screened: 1994 (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1534)
      Director: Jacobson, Fran
    - Title: Gay Rights / Special Rights, Screened: Unknown (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1538)
      Director: [Phipps, Cyrille]
    - Title: Salamander, Screened: [1994] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1541)
    - Title: Mix '95 Trailer, Screened: 1995 (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1602)
    - Title: Topless, Dickless, Clueless, Screened: [1994] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1607)
      Old number: 2
      Director: Summers, AK
    - Title: TEXAS, Screened: [1994] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1609)
      Director: [MKG]
    - Title: Alimentiveness, Screened: Unkonwn (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1644)
    - Title: Jane, Screened: Unknown (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1645)
    - Title: Love of 3 Oranges, Screened: Unknown (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1646)
      Old number: 64449
      Director: Uman, Naomi
    - Title: Anastasia and the Queen of Hearts, Screened: [1998] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1647)
      Old number: T118
      Director: Atkins, Shawn
    - Title: Lily and Lulu Go to the March, Screened: [1994] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1648)
      Director: Marnell, Lily and Luciana Moreira
    - Title: Las Cosas Que El Me Hizo Que Hacer, Screened: [1994] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1733)
      Old number: 239
    - Title: She Makes Love with Her, Screened: [1992] (Box 20, Folder ID: 143.1745)
  - Subseries H: Ticket Sales
    - Box office and merchandising figures, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 656)
    - Festival and press passes, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 657)
  - Subseries I: Outreach
    - Archive Project - Visual AIDS, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 658)
    - Asia Society, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 659)
    - Brooklyn AIDS Task Force calendar, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 660)
    - Columbia Lesbian Bisexual and Gay Coalition fundraiser flyer, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 661)
    - Fund for the City of New York Computer Exchange, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 662)
    - Gay and Lesbian Media Coalition - Help Wanted ad, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 663)
    - New York Pride Guide, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 664)
    - The Pulse fundraiser flyer, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 665)
    - Shades of Lavender calendars and newsletter, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 666)
  - Subseries J: Grants/Fundraising
    - Fundraising - letter format, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 667)
    - Grant research (DISKETTE INCLUDED), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 668)
    - Lists of potential funders, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 669)
    - Astraea, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 670)
    - Canadian Consulate General, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 671)
    - Chicago Resource Center, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 672)
    - Deer Creek Foundation, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 673)
    - Evian, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 674)
    - Film/Video Arts, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 675)
    - Hiram Walker, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 676)
    - HX advertising rates, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 677)
    - Manhattan Community Arts Fund, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 678)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 679)
    - National Geographic Television Grant, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 680)
    - National Guide to Gay and Lesbian Funding, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 681)
    - New York Council of the Humanities, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 682)
    - New York Foundation, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 683)
    - New York Online (DISKETTE INCLUDED), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 684)
    - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 685)
    - New York State Council of the Arts - cultural services contract, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 686)
    - Andy Warhol Foundation, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 687)
- SERIES IX: 1995
  This series contains materials pertaining to the ninth year of the Festival. Subseries D (electronic database) does not exist for this series.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Advertising profile, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 688)
    - Expenses - Financial statements, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 689)
    - Expenses - Financial summary (blank), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 689a.)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 690)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 691)
    - Expenses - Materials for the Arts (inc. invoices and correspondence), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 692)
    - Expenses - National Westminster Bank statements, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 693)
    - Expenses - Petty cash envelopes, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 694)
    - Expenses - Pitney Bowes meter rental bill, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 695)
    - Expenses - Pre-box study, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 696)
    - Expenses - Tax exemption form, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 697)
    - Expenses - Telephone (AT+T, NYNEX, Sprint, Working Assets), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 698)
    - Expenses - Telephone (GLAAD joint account), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 699)
    - Festival statements - Call for media works and curatorial proposals, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 700)
    - Festival statements - Press release, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 701)
    - Hospitality - Guest accreditation forms, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 702)
    - Hospitality - Misc. correspondence and documents, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 703)
    - Legal - Signed curators' contracts, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 704)
    - Legal - PopSmear contract, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 705)
    - Letterhead - Fax cover sheets (blank), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 706)
    - Mailing lists - Filmmakers, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 707)
    - Mailing lists - Staff and committee, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 708)
    - Mailing lists - Press, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 709)
    - Mailing lists - Rolodex, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 710)
    - Notes - Budgets - Black Nation/Queer Nations?, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 711)
    - Notes - Budgets - Festival, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 712)
    - Notes - Mix Festival (general), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 713)
    - Notes - Party research, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 714)
    - Notes - Press research, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 715)
    - Notes - Press screenings/sponsorship, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 716)
    - Notes - Volunteers, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 717)
    - Notes - misc., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 718)
    - Postal - Bulk mail information, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 719)
    - Postal - Mix envelopes, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 720)
    - Programming - Selection process, film lists with scores, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 721)
    - Programming - Selection process, film lists with scores, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 722)
    - Programming - Scheduling, guest curators' programs, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 723)
    - Programming - Program guide, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 724)
    - Programming - Program listings, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 725)
    - Programming - Schedules, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 726)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence
    - Correspondence from filmmakers and film/arts organizations, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 727)
    - Correspondence - Shari Frilot, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 728)
    - Correspondence - Afterparties, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 729)
    - Correspondence - Bavo Defurne, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 730)
    - Correspondence - Free Speech TV, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 731)
    - Correspondence - Joshua Gamson (contains sociology paper on Mix, "Show Me Yours: Negotiating Collective Identity in Lesbian and Gay Film Festivals;" rebuttal paper from Sarah Schulman, "A Samoan Talks Back to Margaret Mead;" correspondence from Gamson to Schulman), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 732)
    - Correspondence - Rejection letter, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 733)
  - Subseries C: Entry Forms/Press Kits (see also Oversize series)
    - Entry forms - 100 Years of Sodomy program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 734)
    - Entry forms - Black Nations/Queer Nations? program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 735)
    - Entry forms - Chill Out/Dont Rhine installation, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 736)
    - Entry forms - Close Encounters program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 737)
    - Entry forms - Cybertopia program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 738)
    - Entry forms - Demons program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 739)
    - Entry forms - Desire in the Urban Landscape program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 740)
    - Entry forms - Divas in Training program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 741)
    - Entry forms - Drag Explosion program (DISK INCLUDED), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 742)
    - Entry forms - Fagsploitation, Baby! program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 743)
    - Entry forms - Generation Sex program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 744)
    - Entry forms - Girls Girls Girls program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 745)
    - Entry forms - History program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 746)
    - Entry forms - Hot 'n' Sticky program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 747)
    - Entry forms - Hot off the Cutting Board program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 748)
    - Entry forms - Idealized Bodies program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 749)
    - Entry forms - Jungli Boogie program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 750)
    - Entry forms - No More Sweets for You program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 751)
    - Entry forms - Omelette program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 752)
    - Entry forms - Pornographic Imagination program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 753)
    - Entry forms - Puppetoons: Dolls and Animation program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 754)
    - Entry forms - Queer Family Skeletons program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 755)
    - Entry forms - Rapture program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 756)
    - Entry forms - Scorched Terrain: AIDS program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 757)
    - Entry forms - Snow Queens program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 758)
    - Entry forms - So Funny It Hurts program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 759)
    - Entry forms - Vaginal Creme Davis Love Train program (CASSETTE and 2 7" RECORDS INCLUDED), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 760)
    - Entry forms - Vintage: Families of Value program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 761)
    - Entry forms - Vulva Riot program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 762)
    - Entry forms - Curatorial proposals, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 763)
    - Entry forms - Curatorial proposals, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 764)
    - Entry forms - Curatorial proposals ("originals"), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 765)
    - Entry forms - Installation applications, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 766)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, A-F, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 767)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, G-L, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 768)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, M-R, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 769)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, S-Z, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 770)
  - Subseries E: Press/Promotion/Posters (see also Oversize/Mapcase series)
    - Artsnews - Mix 95 mention, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 772)
    - GiRl - "Fast Forward: Your Queer Movie Video Guide", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 773)
    - HX - "Hot 'n' Sticky? Vulva Riots? Snow Queens?", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 776)
    - HX - Mix mentions in Homo Musts and Linda Simpson's Drag Update, Mix 95 ad, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 777)
    - Knitting Factory Knotes - Schedule for Mix 95, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 778)
    - Metroline - "Going Celluloid with Mix 95", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 780)
    - Monitor - Mix 95 article, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 781)
    - New York - Mix mention in Cue: Movies section, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 782)
    - New York Press - Mix mention in "Calendar: November 1-7", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 783)
    - New York Times - Mix mention in Arts and Leisure section, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 784)
    - Screw - "The Gay's the Thing", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 785)
    - Time Out New York - Mix 95 Festival highlights and preview, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 786)
    - Village Voice - "Edgy, Sexy, Cool", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 788)
    - Afterparties - Flyers and information, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 789)
    - Afterparties - Hudson Grill flyer, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 790)
    - Mix 95 postcards, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 791)
    - Poster - designs, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 793)
  - Subseries F: Special Programs (see also Oversize series)
    - A Different Take - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 795)
    - Black Nations/Queer Nations? - Project info and correspondence, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 797)
    - CEPA Gallery - Power and Desire off the Margins showcase, curated by Larry Brose - flyers, invoices, notes, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 798)
    - Cybertopia at Knitting Factory - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 800)
    - Mix Brasil - Correspondence, invoices, program listings, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 801)
    - Mix Brussels - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 802)
    - Mix Magazine and Guia Mix, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 803)
    - Mix Sydney, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 804)
  - Subseries G: Media
    - Title: 607, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0605)
      Director: Thompson, Walter
    - Title: Be Careful What Kind of Skin You Pull Back, You Never Know What Kind of Head Will Appear, Screened: 1994 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0606)
      Old number: 4
      Director: Bruning, Jurgen
    - Title: Naomi's Legacy, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0607)
    - Title: Between These Few Silent Breaths, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0608)
      Director: Komisar, Lucinda
    - Title: Stolen Shadows, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0609)
      Old number: 9
      Director: Grandell, Steve and Killacky, John
    - Title: AIDS' Dark Terrain: Twelve Stations from a Yankee Pilgrim, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0610)
      Director: Tichane, Robin
    - Title: [1.]--Ice Cream Sunday [2.]--Sexlock!, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0611)
      Director: [2.]--Cowan, Jeff
    - Title: Leather, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0612)
      Old number: 12
      Director: Haberman, Hardy
    - Title: Out for a change: Addressing homophobia in women's sports, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0613)
      Distributor: additional credits: Woman Vision
    - Title: Eight, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0614)
      Director: Gray, Elaine
    - Title: Intimate Relationships in Two Lesbian Families Living in American Society, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0615)
      Director: [Asten, Dr. Maureen]
    - Title: What I'm Thinking, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0616)
      Director: Malaran, Barbara
    - Title: Personally Yours, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0617)
      Director: Robinson, Jeff
    - Title: Sherry Vine's Real, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0618)
      Director: Adam, Kevin
    - Title: Cowboy Jesus, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0619)
      Director: Yerkes, Jamie
    - Title: Days of Pentecost, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0620)
      Director: Elbert, Lawrence
    - Title: Borders, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0621)
      Old number: 24
      Director: Gelmini, Elio
    - Title: Out in South Africa, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0622)
      Director: Hammer, Barbara
    - Title: Konichiwa Oldies, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0623)
      Director: Sbrizzi, Paul
      Distributor: distributed by: Combo Productions
      Duration: 110 minutes
    - Title: Bottom, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0624)
      Director: [Chiu, Terry]
    - Title: "Pull," a Portrait of David Nunsmaher, Screened: 1995 (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0625)
      Old number: 29
      Director: Sherman, Stuart
    - Title: Letter To My Grandma, Screened: [1995] (Box 21, Folder ID: 143.0626)
      Old number: 30
      Director: Howe, Alyssa Cymene
    - Title: Rocketlipsbabblon, Screened: 1995 (Box 22, Folder ID: 143.0627)